Guide to the Duke Photography Faculty and Staff Photographs, circa 1960s-2003 UA.12.03.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Faculty and Staff Photographs, 1
  - Peterson, Andrew, 1231
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Peterson, Eric, 1232
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Petroski, Catherine, 1233
    - Photographs (Box 17)
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Petroski, Henry, 1234
    - Photographs (Box 17)
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Petters, Arlie, 1235
    - Photographs (Box 17)
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Pfeiffer, Steven, 1236
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Phelps, Leland, 1237
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Phillips, Dickson, 1238
    - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Phillips, George, 1239
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Phillips, Harry, 1240
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Pickens, Sarah, 1241
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pickus, Noah, 1242
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pierce, Michael, 1243
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pietrantoni, Joe, 1244
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Pilchuk, Cindy, 1245
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pilkey, Orrin, 1246
    - Photographs (Box 18)
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Pilkington, Deborah, 1247
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pilkington, Theo, 1248
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pimm, Stuart, 1249
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Piot, Charlie, 1250
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pippen, Jeffrey, 1251
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pirrung, Michael, 1252
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pisetsky, David, 1253
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Piva, John, 1254
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Piver, Warren, 1255
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pizzo, Sal, 1256
    - Photographs (Box 18)
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Platt, Jeffrey, 1257
    - Photographs (Box 18)
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Plonsey, Robert, 1258
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Plummer, Ellen, 1259
    - Photographs (Box 18)
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Politi, Elizabetta, 1260
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Polzien, Kristen, 1261
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pope, Deborah, 1262
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pope-Levison, Priscilla, 1263
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Porter, Joe, 1264
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Porter, Ned, 1265
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Powell, Jefferson, 1266
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Powell, Richard, 1267
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Powell, Ted, 1268
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pradhan, Ash, 1269
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Pransue, 1270
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Prasad, Leela, 1271
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pratson, Lincoln, 1272
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pratt Edmund [file 0842-00], 1273
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pratt, Edmund, 1274
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Pratt, Vernon, 1275
    - Photographs (Box 18)
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Preyar, Monica, 1276
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Preziosi, Karen, 1277
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Price, David, 1278
    - Photographs (Box 18)
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Price, Libby, 1279
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Price, Marva, 1280
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Price, Matthew, 1281
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Price, Reynolds, 1282
    - Photographs (Box 18)
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Prisant, Michael, 1283
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Pritchard, Eric, 1284
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Proctor, Samuel, 1285
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Prose, Neil, 1286
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Provenzale, Jim, 1287
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Pryer, Kathleen, 1288
    - Photographs (Box 18)
    - Negatives (Box 37)
  - Puckett, Andrew, 1289
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Purves, Dale, 1290
    - Photographs (Box 18)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Putman, Charles E., 1291
    - Photographs (Box 18)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Pyatt, Tim, 1292
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Qualls, Robert, 1293
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Quillian, Ruth, 1294
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Radway, Janice, 1295
    - Photographs (Box 18)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Raetz, Chris, 1296
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Ramachandran, Vijaya, 1297
    - Photographs (Box 18)
  - Rami, Fred, 1298
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Randall, Dale, 1299
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Randolph, David, 1300
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rankin, Thomas, 1301
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Raspberry, William, 1302
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rausher, Mark, 1303
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Reavis, Sonny, 1304
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Reckhow, Kenneth, 1305
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Redmond, Domonique, 1306
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Reed, Michael, 1307
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - CDs (Box 25)
  - Reed, Robert, 1309
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Reedy, Mike, 1310
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Reents-Budet, Dorie, 1311
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Reese, Ben, 1312
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Reichert, William Monty, 1313
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Reif, John, 1314
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Reinheimer, Bob, 1315
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Remmer, Karen, 1316
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rendell, Ed, 1317
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Reppy, Bill, 1318
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Revelo, Maggie, 1319
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Reves, Jerry, 1320
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Reynolds, James, 1321
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Richards, John, 1322
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Richardson, Curtis, 1323
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Richey, Russell, 1324
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Richie, Maurice, 1325
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Richter, Dan, 1326
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Riddell, Richard, 1327
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Riley, Ann, 1328
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rimer, Barbara, 1329
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rimmler, Jackie, 1330
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Roberts, Carmichael, 1331
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Roberts, Pauline, 1332
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Roberts, Vern, 1333
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Robertson, Cary, 1334
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Robertson, Horace B., 1335
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Robertson, Robbie, 1336
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Robinson, Lisa, 1337
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Robinson, Sally, 1338
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Robinson, Thomas, 1339
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Robisheaux, Tom, 1340
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rockey, Don, 1341
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Rodas, Don, 1342
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rodger, Susan, 1343
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rogers, Mark, 1344
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Rohrman, Doug, 1345
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Rojstaczer, Stuart, 1346
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Roland, Alex, 1347
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Rolleston, James, 1348
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Rose, Hilary, 1349
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rose, Jed, 1350
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Rose, Liana, 1351
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Roselius, Becky, 1352
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Rosemond, Crusty, 1353
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Rosenberg, Alex, 1354
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rosenberg, Paul, 1355
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rosenquist, Valerie, 1356
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Roses, Alan, 1357
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Ross, Ruth, 1358
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Ross, Susan, 1359
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rosse, Wendell, 1360
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Roth, Susan, 1361
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Roush, Patricia, 1362
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Rowe, Tom, 1363
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Royal, Steve, 1364
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Royster, Marc, 1365
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rubin, David, 1366
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Ruderman, Judith, 1367
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Rudy, Kathy, 1368
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Ruff, Gregory, 1369
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rumer, Ralph, 1370
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Rusak, Stacy, 1371
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Ryan, Thomas, 1372
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Saling, Patricia, 1373
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 38)
  - Sampson, John, 1374
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Sandoe-Thorp, Ann, 1375
    - Photographs (Box 19)
  - Sandstrom, Marlene, 1376
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Sanford, Terry, 1377
    - Photographs (Box 20)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Sasson, Diane, 1378
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Saunders, Ann, 1379
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Savarese, John, 1380
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Savino, Michael, 1381
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Scannell, Angela, 1382
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Scarpucci, Penny, 1383
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Scearce, Richard, 1384
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schaeffer, David, 1385
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schanberg, Saul, 1386
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Schandberg, Rachel, 1387
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Scharf, Gil, 1388
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Schauman, Sally, 1389
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schelsinger, William, 1390
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Schiffman, Susan, 1391
    - Photographs (Box 20)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Schlesinger, William, 1392
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schmader, Kenneth, 1393
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Schmalbeck, Richard, 1394
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schmechel, Don, 1395
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schmidt, Evelyn, 1396
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Schmidt, Ginny, 1397
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schmidt, Ron, 1398
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schmidt, Silke, 1399
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schmidt-Nielsen, Knut, 1400
    - Photographs (Box 20)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Schrage, Mike, 1401
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schroeder, Christopher, 1402
    - Photographs (Box 20)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Schultz, Caleb, 1403
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schusterman, Tamara, 1404
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schwanter, Joseph, 1405
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schwarcz, Steve, 1406
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schwartz, David, 1407
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schwartz, David, 1408
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Schwartz, John A., 1409
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Schwartz, Rochelle, 1410
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Scott, Andre, 1411
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Scott, Ann, 1412
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Sedgwick, Eve, 1413
    - Photographs (Box 20)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - See, Nancy, 1414
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Seigler, Hilliard, 1415
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Semans, James, 1416
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Semans, Mary and James, 1417
    - Photographs (Box 20)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Semilof, Alex, 1418
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Seo, David, 1419
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Serls, Gayle, 1420
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Seskovitch, John, 1421
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Setton, Lori, 1422
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Sexton, Daniel, 1423
    - Photographs (Box 20)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Shanahan, Suzanne, 1424
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Shanawani, Hasan, 1425
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Shannon, Laurie, 1426
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Share, Katherine, 1427
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Shatzmiller, Joseph, 1428
    - Photographs (Box 20)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Shaw, Colin, 1429
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Shaw, Nancy, 1430
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Shea, Jim, 1431
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Shearer, Sheila, 1432
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Sheegog, Jim, 1433
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Sheline, Barbara, 1434
    - Photographs (Box 20)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Shepard, Bob, 1435
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Shephard, Marion, 1436
    - Photographs (Box 20)
  - Sheppard, Blair, 1437
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Shields, Dennis, 1438
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Shimm, Mel, 1439
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Shingleton, William, 1440
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Shipley, Bob, 1441
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Shipp, Kathy, 1442
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Shu, Edward, 1443
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Shuler, Andrew, 1444
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Sibley, Greg, 1445
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Sidman, Edwin, 1446
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Siedow, Jim, 1447
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Sieg, Holger, 1448
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Siegel, Lewis, 1449
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Siemer, Richard, 1450
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Sievers, Clause, 1451
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Sigel, Pete, 1452
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Silar, Jackie, 1453
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Silbiger, Kathy, 1454
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Silliman, Scott, 1455
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Simel, Dave, 1456
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Simon, John, 1457
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Simons, Elwyn, 1458
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Simons, Friderun, 1459
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Sinder, Janet, 1460
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Skender, C. J., 1461
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Skene, Pat, 1462
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Skinner, Cellette, 1463
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Skotko, Brian, 1464
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Sloan, Frank A., 1465
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Slotkin, Theodore, 1466
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Smith, Alice, 1467
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, Barbara Hernstein, 1468
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, Charles Michael, 1469
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, David A., 1470
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, Forrest, 1471
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, Harmon, 1472
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, Jim, 1473
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, Kathleen, 1474
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, Linda, 1475
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, Martin, 1476
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, Moody, 1477
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, Peter K., 1478
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Smith, Robert, 1479
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, S. Schieffelin, 1480
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, Stacey, 1481
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, Steve, 1482
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Smith, V. Kerry, 1483
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Smith, Warren, 1484
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Snook, Laura, 1485
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Snyderman, Judith, 1486
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Snyderman, Ralph, 1487
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Socolar, Joshua, 1488
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Solie, Guy and Family, 1489
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Solomon, Annette, 1490
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Sowell, Ashlyn, 1491
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Sowers, Kevin, 1492
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Spaulding, Jean, 1493
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Speer, Kevin, 1494
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Spengler, Arthur, 1495
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Spenner, Ken, 1496
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Spicer, Leonard, 1497
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Spier, Verna, 1498
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Spohn, Heather, 1499
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Springer, Roxanne P., 1500
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Spruill, Carol, 1501
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Squire, Deborah, 1502
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - St. Clair, William (Bill), 1503
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Stack, Richard, 1504
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Staelin, Rick, 1505
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Stafford-Smit, Mark, 1506
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Stagg, Elizabeth, 1507
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Stallard, Eric, 1508
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Stamler, Jonathan, 1509
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Stangl, Dalene, 1510
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Stanley, Bruce, 1511
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Stanley, John, 1512
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Stapleton, Heather, 1513
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Starn, Orin, 1514
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Stead, Eugene, 1515
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Steckley, Linda, 1516
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Steel, Bob, 1517
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Steffens, David, 1518
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Steinmetz, David, 1519
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Stempen, Bob, 1520
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Stenger, Judith, 1521
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Stenner, Michael, 1522
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Stephens, Bill, 1523
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Stetten, George D., 1524
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Stickel, Delford, 1525
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Stiff-Roberts, Adrienne, 1526
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Stiles, Gary, 1527
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Stiles, Kristine, 1528
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Stinson-Wesley, Amelia, 1529
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Stone, Martin, 1530
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Stone, Ron, 1531
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Stopford, Woodhall, 1532
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Storey, Peter, 1533
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Strain, Boyd, 1534
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Strandberg, Vic, 1535
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Strauman, Tim, 1536
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Strickland, David, 1537
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Strittmatter, Warren, 1538
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Strohbehn, John, 1539
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Struhsaker, Thomas, 1540
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Stuart, Carmon, 1541
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Stubbee, Melinda, 1542
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Stubbing, Richard, 1543
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Suarez, Edward, 1544
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Sugarman, Jeremy, 1545
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 40)
  - Sullenger, Bruce, 1546
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Sullivan, Marty, 1547
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Sullivan, Robert, 1548
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Sun, Xiaobai, 1549
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Surwit, Richard, 1550
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Swaim, Mark, 1551
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Swansey, John, 1552
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Swanson, Jeffrey, 1553
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Swartwelder, Scott, 1554
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Swenson, Kathy, 1555
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Swinney, Al, 1556
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Taber, Bob, 1557
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Tacket, Danny, 1558
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Takeman, Jeff, 1559
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Taliaferro, Clay, 1560
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Tapson, Vic, 1561
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Tauchen, George, 1562
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Tavernise, Peter, 1563
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Taylor, Curtis, 1564
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Taylor, Donald H., 1565
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Taylor, Doris, 1566
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Taylor, John, 1567
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Taylorsmith, Margaret, 1568
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Tedder, Thomas, 1569
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Telen, Marilyn, 1570
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Terborgh, John, 1571
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Terrell, Allen, 1572
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Tetel, Julie, 1573
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Tetel, Marcel, 1574
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Thom, Jennifer, 1575
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Thomann, Wayne, 1576
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Thomas, John, 1577
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Thomas, R. David, 1578
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Thomas, Richard, 1579
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Thompson, Bob, 1580
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Thompson, George, 1581
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Thompson, John, 1582
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Thompson, Peter, 1583
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Thorne, Ro, 1584
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Tifft, Susan, 1585
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Tiley, Wade, 1586
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Timberlake, Bob, 1587
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Timmer, Ashley, 1588
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Timmins, Chris, 1589
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Timmons, Phil, 1590
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Tiryakian, Edward, 1591
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Tobias, Randall, 1592
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Todd, Larry, 1593
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Toleza, Eric, 1594
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Tolsma, John, 1595
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Tomasi, Carlo, 1596
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Tompkins, Jane, 1597
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Toone, Eric, 1598
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Torgovinick, Marianna, 1599
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Toth, Cynthia, 1600
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Tower, Edward, 1601
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Tragenstein, John, 1602
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Trahey, Greg, 1603
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Transue, John, 1604
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Trask, Tallman III, 1605
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Travis, James, 1606
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Trayler, Steve, 1607
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Treen, Will, 1608
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Treml, Vladimir, 1609
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Trivedi, Kishor, 1610
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Troxler, Rebecca, 1611
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Truskey, George, 1612
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Tubbs, Jerry, 1613
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Tucci, Debara, 1614
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Tucker, Irene, 1615
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Tufts, Claire, 1616
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Tulis, Jerry, 1617
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Tulsky, James, 1618
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Tung, Chen, 1619
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Turner, Dennis, 1620
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Turner, William, 1621
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Tuttle-Newhall, Betsy, 1622
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Tuxill, John, 1623
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Tye, John, 1624
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Tyler, Douglas, 1625
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Tyndall, Nancy, 1626
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Uhlfelder, Michelle, 1627
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Underkuffler, Laura, 1628
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Urbaniak, James, 1629
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Uribe, Martin, 1630
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Utz, John, 1631
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Vail, Thomas, 1632
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Valade, Renee, 1633
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Van Alstyne, William, 1634
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Van Miegroet, Hans, 1635
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Van Schaik, Carel, 1636
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Vance, Jeffrey, 1637
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Various Artists, 1638
    - Photographs (Box 23)
      Folder contains pictures of performing artists, named and unidentified, and cast biographies for a production of A Thousand Clowns, starring Tom Selleck. Identified artists include Mark Blum, Bradford Cover, Barbara Garrick, Nicolas King, Robert LuPone, Joanne Metcalf, and James Tocco. Nine unidentified photographs.
    - Negatives (Box 41)
      Folder contains negatives of performing artists, named and unidentified. Identified artists are Mark Blum,Joanne Brackeen (piano), Bradford Cover, George Cables, Derrick Gardner, Barbara Garrick, and James Tocco. Three unidentified individuals.
  - Vasuvan, Dharni, 1639
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Vaughn, Peter, 1640
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Velazquez, Eric, 1641
    - Photographs (Box 23)